soccershots.org 2016-08-02

# Privacy Policy - Soccer Shots

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for [soccershots.org](http://www.soccershots.org/) and [ssreg.org](http://www.ssreg.org/). This privacy policy applies to the Site itself.

 **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

 **Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any
  * Change/correct any data we have about you
  * Have us delete any data we have about you
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

 **Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

 **Updates  
**Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

 **Orders**  
We request information from you on our registration form. To sign up for Soccer Shots, you must provide contact information and financial information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

 **Cookies**  
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

 **Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

 **Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at   _717-616-8587_ or via email at ****[information@soccershots.org](mailto:information@soccershots.org).**

This document was last updated on December 15, 2016.
